All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, sets sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World, Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island, which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
The Fishman Pirates, led by Horty Jones and assisted by Vander Decken, plot to overthrow King Neptune.
It's not long before the Straw Hats get pulled into the conflict and find themselves in the midst of an all-out war.
Perhaps!
But even if you could stop it, you would still have to go through me first.
And if memory serves, that didn't work out so well last time.
Horty! What's happened to you?
There are people living in the Fishman District who were once your allies!
What you're doing doesn't benefit anyone, not even you!
Why can't you see that, Horty?
Is there something I don't know?
Or is your hatred so deep that you've abandoned your sense of reason entirely?
Tell me the cause of this madness!
Did humans attack you?
Did they torment you in some untold manner?
Did they kill your friends?
Did they hurt your family?
Did they take something you hold dear?
Answer me, dammit!
What did humans do to you that was so unforgivable?
Why?
What in this world could inspire such cruelty?
This is the air tank. We've met before, remember?
Oh, yeah, hey guys!
We've been listening to what's happening out there.
And we can see the Noah hurtling toward the island.
We've begun making the preparations as we've discussed.
Don't make it more complicated! Just go for it, okay?
And Luffy, everyone here is counting on you.
Can you hear me, Straw Hat?
Please, listen. He spoke earlier and… It's clear now. Gordy is… Gordy! Gordy?
Yes! Gordy!
Yes!
J-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-J-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-jj-j-j-j-j.
Shocking fact, the true identity of Horty.
Earlier that day, before the Noah began its descent on the island,
it was a very good one.
Whoa!
Oh, my knee!
Oh!
You jerk!
You really made me mad, you know that?
Oh!
This is what you get!
Intimidation!
Megabuck!
Come on, it was big enough already!
Am I supposed to be impressed?
Well, you're surprised, right?
I'm a Tiger Blowfish Fishman!
Scary, huh?
Not really.
Kinda curious why you're talking like that, though.
Cause I'll deflate if I keep my mouth open, you idiot!
I could...
The Kraken is still way bigger than you.
Oh, yeah?
Fine!
Then how about this?
Blue House D!
How annoying!
Don't crush me, dammit!
Stop it!
What is zooming?
We're on your side!
You're squashing all of us!
Still a shrimp compared to the Kraken.
Impossible!
Blue House D!
Good job, you moron!
We have come, your majesty!
Are you all right down there?
I'm so sorry, my king!
We should have been able to protect you, and we failed!
We're pathetic, worthless vassals!
Worthless vassals!
Never mind that.
More importantly, did you see the Noah?
Yes.
Tragic that it's been moved under such circumstances.
Curse you, Deccan.
I never thought you would sink so low as to destroy your own island.
And your own people.
Trust me, Your Majesty.
We were just as shocked as you were.
We even tried to order an island-wide evacuation.
But those new fishmen pirate bastards are blocking any transmission.
Even worse, we haven't been able to make contact with the bloodguards out at sea.
Prepare to shoot the bubble now!
Hurry!
See?
They won't pick up.
You need to get the king out of here in some place safe now.
No.
Huh?
I'm waiting right here for the princes.
What in blazes?
Someone explain this.
What's happening?
Like, for starters, where did all these damn pirates come from?
Well, sir?
The straw hats are on our side?
Jimbe.
And the princess?
Forty.
Deccan.
So that's what happened.
All right, men.
Everything is clear to me now.
All of you, to the plaza.
Follow Jimbe.
Back up the straw hats.
If the straw hats can handle the more powerful fighters,
our men can suppress the others.
It's insane.
We tried to arrest them, yet they're fighting to save our island.
We should be ashamed for not trusting them.
It's time to make things right and give them our support.
Great.
It's Neptune's army.
Hey, no big deal.
We can crush them.
Kill them all.
Stand tall and show these bastards what we're made of.
Why the hell is a human fighting us?
Move, slaves.
Attack.
Get out there and fight for us unless you want to die.
Hum-o-hum-o-hum-o.
Hurry up.
March, slave tank.
Turn right and head that way.
Whoopsie.
Worthless klutz.
Just drag the bastard.
Look at that pathetic flesh bag.
Replace him.
Come on.
Come-o-hum-o-hum-o.
That's truly disgusting.
They all reek of hypocrisy.
Nico Robin.
Could you perhaps use your power to free those slaves?
Really?
Are you sure that's wise?
They won't care for fishmen.
I'll knock them unconscious if they try to take their grudge out on me.
Because the life that they're living right now, they're even lower than beasts.
This behavior was learned from the Celestial Dragons.
I won't stand for it.
All right.
Count on me.
Thank you.
Let's go!
Pick up the pace, you trash!
Hum-o-hum-o-hum-o-hum-o.
All our callers.
They came off.
Hey!
What's the deal here?
The hell?
Who's taking the callers off of the slaves?
Hey, woman.
You're a straw hat, aren't you?
Turn around and face me when I'm talking to you.
Oh-oh-oh.
What the hell is wrong with you worthless slaves?
We're free.
Was it you?
Why save us when we were fighting against you?
I can't say no to a handsome man.
In other words, thank Boss Jinbei.
Jinbei?
But...
How dare you!
They're mine!
Troll net!
Hum-o-hum-o-hum-o-hum!
Let's put you in chains!
Web-o-fleur!
What the hell?
This is getting weird!
No!
Cut that out!
Just relax.
This won't take long.
Let go!
Hang on!
How are there two of you?
A-ah!
Double!
She got Hammond!
Will do, sir!
Thanks a whole lot for the help, lady.
You bastards treated us like trash.
I'm gonna pay you back for every beating you gave me and then some.
The enemy just freed all our slaves.
It's a room of walls!
No!
Yes!
Put-a-put-put-put-put-put-put-put-put-put-put-put-put-put-put-put-put-put-put-put-put-put-put-put-put.
Click.
This is the border guard patrol calling, sir.
Have I reached the minister of the left?
You have?
I've been frantically trying to call you over and over again.
Why didn't you pick up?
I don't mean to be insolent, sir.
But I'm afraid there's no time for me to explain with our situation.
Please, you need to warn the whole kingdom.
It's the NOAA, sir.
We've just been informed it's lost power.
As a result, it's begun falling again, and it's hurtling towards the island.
Surely not!
What could this mean?
Where are you calling from?
The air tank, sir. From the control tower.
That's good. That means you can warn everyone about the impending danger.
All our communication centers are down.
But you can help.
You can contact the state-operated transponder snails all across the country.
Please hurry.
Yes, sir.
This is an emergency announcement to all citizens of the Ryugu Kingdom.
An evacuation has been issued.
The giant ship, known as the NOAA, is falling towards Fishman Island.
Everyone must flee the area immediately.
I repeat, the NOAA is descending on the island.
Everyone must flee immediately or face certain destruction.
Is this for real?
Look up there!
The NOAA. You can see it.
Is Deccan behind this?
What? Are you really that surprised?
That damn creepy stalker.
I can't believe he would go this far.
The bubble's gonna break!
The island will be destroyed!
Keep running. Just forget about your stuff.
What?
Get out of here! Quick!
Everybody move it! The NOAA is coming!
Did something bad happen?
I heard the princess was drawing the ship away from the island.
Yeah, I'm worried about her.
We can't just swim off and abandon her now.
What about the NOAA crashing into the island do you not get?
I just...
Do you guys really want to waste the princess's effort by staying here and dying?
We have to leave the island!
To the sea!
Come on! Hurry!
Oh, jeez. That thing's falling again?
Damn.
You better fix this mess quick, Luffy.
Something must have happened to Princess Shirohoshi.
What's Deccan trying to pull?
That crazy son of a bitch.
We've got no choice but to run.
That ship will kill us all.
You can leave Horty and his associates to us.
All of you citizens are ordered to flee the island.
Now get going!
What's wrong with you?
I said go!
No way!
Wait. What?
Women and children especially!
Come on! Move it!
We told you now!
The Straw Hats may be a bunch of human pirates, but they're all down there fighting to save our island!
We can't just run away and let them die when they're trying to help us!
Uh... he's right.
Hmm?
We asked them to help us, and I'm not going to turn my back on them.
I can't fight with them, but I won't leave them here to die and run away!
Yes, exactly!
It's the least we can do!
Huh?
Quiet!
All of you!
Listen up!
I'm assigning you a duty.
Tell every other spectator they need to evacuate right now!
If you're going to stay, then save the others while you're here.
Is that understood?
I don't have time to argue with you about it.
So if you want to stay behind, suit yourself!
All right, outlaws!
Time to face my wrath!
Is this Straw Hat Luffy?
All right, it's the air tank.
We've met once before, remember?
What is this?
They're broadcasting to the pirates?
We've heard everything.
We are prepared to take action.
We can see the Noah hurtling toward the island as we speak.
Oh, Luffy!
I don't know what to do!
Do you hear those fools?
They're broadcasting their conversation across the entire country!
Hey, guys!
What do we need to do to get a little air from you?
We can shoot out all the air in the air tank.
If we create a big bubble and shoot it, maybe it'll surround the Noah.
Shiro Hoshi!
Straw Hat!
I'm afraid that's all we can do.
After we deploy the bubble, the rest is up to you.
Don't make it more complicated!
Just go for it, okay?
Luffy's still all right.
Thank goodness.
He sounds as optimistic as ever.
Hey, come on!
It's Luffy we're talking about!
I knew he'd be okay!
I don't understand what's going on!
What is he doing here?
And more than that, what's the princess doing with him?
Yeah, the Straw Hat guy's the one who kidnapped her, right?
He's a human!
And Luffy, everyone here is counting on you.
Anyone else confused why the Border Guard's asking a human pirate to save the island?
Hold on, does this mean that the human is on board the Noah?
So is he trying to stop it?
Can you hear me, Straw Hat?
What?
Prince Spook of Ocean?
He spoke earlier and...
It's clear now.
Hordy is...
Keep talking!
Just tell us what Hordy is already!
He's not a fish man.
He's a monster brought to life by our hatred.
Their hatred?
What is he talking about?
The new fish man pirates.
They're nothing but remnants of a grudge from ages past.
We allowed their evil to fester in the shadow of Fishman Island.
And they began to champion this meaningless grudge.
Flying its flag in some misguided sense of pride.
They fear a future without it.
In truth, they want humans to be evil.
Otherwise, there is no reason to justify their crusade.
All they desire is bloodshed.
And despite what they say,
they don't want peace for fish man either.
Answer me, damn it!
What did humans do to you that was so unforgivable?
Why?
What in this world could inspire such cruelty?
That's not one damn thing?
Hmm...
Not one damn thing.
That... that's your answer?
Ugh!
Uh...
The simple truth.
We were chosen by heaven to punish the humans.
That's our purpose.
And we have the power to do so.
I understand now this sick and pathetic truth.
All of their fury, their hatred, it doesn't come from experience or logic or fact.
They have no substance.
Just empty cruelty.
Horty's hatred runs wild as Luffy continues to struggle in his undersea battle.
A single shot of air fired from Fishman Island is Luffy's only hope.
Yet even if the oxygen on the Noah is restored and Horty defeated, the ship itself could doom the island.
Luffy vows to save the fishmen below, but their lives may never be the same.
On the next One Piece, back to zero, earnest wishes for Luffy.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates.
Pastives quote onweise.
Will Northe territoireula towards Horty Be Хut owns tes cheats.
When Jeremy reaffirm loosed tutaj is not the cinq.
I don't know how you dis où they will.
A cuerpo his ch reins was wounded.
I believe we are tough in this coffin.
Why do they focus on unless he's possessed or a healthcare qur?
Aren't we not addressed?
It's Oxen один.
Is fair enough for us.
Are we so sad?
What are wemış?
It's New Stress glute.
Jordanement doesn't know.
Because we thought, you know what?
I don't believe these things.
If we fight again, you know what happened.
Go away.